On Self Realization and Sahaja Yoga
自觉与霎哈嘉瑜伽
as soon as you start any work in any place, first of all they want Me to cure people
当你在任何地方开始任何工作 首先 他们想让你治疗人们
and to help them with curatives
用各种疗法来帮助他们
Now if I pay attention more to that, then the main work is to create doctors out of everyone
现在如果我放更多的注意力在那些事上 那么主要的工作就是让人们都成为医生
That is neglected. Then you become unpopular. They think, “Oh, She is not sympathetic” and this and that
不是那样的 然后你变得不受欢迎 他们想 噢 祂没有同情心 这个那个
But now as we have everybody can cure now everyone, I don’t cure anyone directly
但现在由于我们每个人都能治疗别人 我不用直接治疗任何人
But they don’t like it. They want I should be there and then you to be pampered and all those things are there, rather difficult
但他们不喜欢那样 他们想让我在那里 满足他们的自我 所有的那些事 相当困难
It’s not that we are not running an election, you see
我们并不是在竞选
like we should please others, sort of this is not there. whatever is the reality
好像我们应该取悦人 不是这样 我们的事都是真实的
if a person has intelligence – pure intelligence
如果一个人有智力 纯粹的智力
he can see that this is something very different
他会看到 这是非常不同的事
and for that one has to understand that you cannot
为此 我们必须明白你不能
you cannot force on anyone that you get your realization
你不能强迫任何人得到自觉
In the same way you cannot force Me that I give you realization
同样地 你也不能强迫我给予你自觉
because if it does not work it does not work. It’s such a living force you see
因为如果它不起作用它就不会起作用 它是一个活生生的力量 你看
and that upsets them very soon.
而且那很快会使他们心烦意乱
I feel that the way this industrial revolution has come in the west
我感到 在西方这场工业革命到来的方式
people have lost their moorings. Perhaps they are so confused
使人们不知在何处停泊 也许他们如此迷惑
With all these gurus coming down here confusing them
所有这些导师来到这里令他们迷惑
and all kinds of new things coming, they don’t know where to look.
各种新事物来到 他们不知该看向哪里
But unless and until you get your evolution completed
但除非你的进化得以完成
unless and until you reach that absolute state of understanding
除非你达到绝对理解的状态
the chaos will remain
否则混乱仍将继续
So one has to try to get to that
因此 一个人必须尽力达到那
But one must understand you can’t pay for it
但必须明白你不能为此而付费
There is no effort
无需费力